### **My Contact**



surajsingh26112002@gmail.com



+918418030135



Vadodara, Gujarat

Linkedin id-https://www.linkedin.com/in/suraj-singh-2858701b9

### **Objective**

To become a successful expert in the field of Information Technology and Management by channelizing my technical knowledge and Management skills to ensure personal and professional growth and to contribute to the prosperity of the organization.

### **Hard Skill**

- Python
- google analysis
- 3D navigation
- HR(human resource)
- Quality and assurance

#### Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-taskina
- · leadership quality

### **Education Background**

### Parul University

B.Tech computer science engineering completed in 2024 with 8.11 CGPA

#### • Mahatma J.F Public school (CBSE)

- 12th (PCM)completed in 2020 with 72.2%
- 10th completed in 2018 with 75.2%

### Certificate

Completed certificate course in following:-

- Learning Canva
- · Stock Investing
- Human resource
- Interviewing techniques
- AR Navigation
- Advance Google Analytics
- Google Digital Unlock
- Python from GUVI
- Game Development with Unity
- Al with GUVI

## Project

**B.Tech CSE** 

Completed minor project on food delivery website frontend

**SURAJ SINGH** 

- Completed minor project on flappy bird game by using unity.
- Worked on major project AR Navigation.

### **Professional Experience**

#### **VARA TECHNOLOGY**

JUNE 2024-Currently working here.

#### **EDU-VERSITY (DATA SCIENCE INTERNSHIP)**

JAN 2024-APR 2024

Key responsibility

- · Worked on python language and mostly use beautifulsoup
- · Analyzing market trends

#### ILP OVERSEAS | HUMAN RESOURCE OFFICER (Internship)

DEC 2022-FEB 2023

Roles & Responsibilities :-

- 1. Posting job advertisements to job boards and social media platforms.
- 2. Screening Potential employees resume and application form to identify suitable candidates.
- 3. Organising Telephonic Interview with Shortlisted Candidates.
- 4. Update your work on GOOGLE FORM by the end of the day.

#### CvDragon || Campus Ambassador internship

MAY 2021-NOV 2021

Key responsibility

- maintenance of record
- communication

# Henry Harvin India Education LLP|| Campus Ambassador internship

2020 OCT-NOV

Key responsibility

- · Promotion activity
- maintenance of record
- communication

### **Achievements**

Coordinator in Projection 2021 in university

Volunteering in Hare krishna movement

Member of Chhatra Sansad School of leadership

SAP USA Certification of Technical consultant.

Gold medalist in NPTEL Internet of Things with 90%

### **Declaration**

I'll hereby declare that all the details mentioned above are in accordance with the truth and fact as per my knowledge and I hold the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars."